[
    {
      "title": "Round 2: 2020 Events"
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which city hosted the 2020 Summer Olympics (though held in 2021 due to the global pandemic)?",
      "answer": "Tokyo, Japan"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "In the November 2020 election, Joe Biden was elected as the ____ President of the United States.",
      "answer": "46th"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which Netflix docu-series about a big-cat zoo owner named Joe Exotic became a pop-culture phenomenon in 2020?",
      "answer": "Tiger King"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which Disney live-action remake, planned for release in March 2020, had its theatrical debut delayed and then partially released on Disney+?",
      "answer": "Mulan"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which music superstar released the surprise album ‘Folklore’ in July 2020?",
      "answer": "Taylor Swift"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "In which month of 2020 did the WHO formally declare the COVID-19 outbreak a pandemic?",
      "answer": "March 2020"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which streaming platform premiered the acclaimed miniseries ‘The Queen’s Gambit’ in October 2020?",
      "answer": "Netflix"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which English football club ended a 30-year wait for the league title by winning the 2019–20 Premier League in June 2020?",
      "answer": "Liverpool F.C."
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which global union did the United Kingdom officially exit on January 31, 2020?",
      "answer": "The European Union (EU)"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which African country was declared free of wild polio virus by the WHO in August 2020, completing Africa’s eradication of wild polio?",
      "answer": "Nigeria"
    }
  ]